Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.9
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 9, 1.
  - District 9 Incoming William Yager Correspondence, April 16, 1936-September 25, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Carey Regarding Mallory and Organization, November 14, 1936; 2.
    - Carey Regarding Indianapolis Organization, January 20, 1937; 3.
    - Carey Regarding Indianapolis RCA and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 23, 1937; 4.
    - Carey Regarding Local 1003 and Dues, May 13, 1937; 5.
    - Carey Regarding Indiana Organization, May 25, 1937; 6.
    - Carey Regarding 1937 UE Convention, August 16, 1937; 7.
    - Carey Regarding Indianapolis Visit, October 30, 1937; 8.
    - Carey Regarding Local 902, January 9, 1940; 9.
    - Carey Secretary Regarding Fort Wayne Visit, January 15, 1940; 10.
    - Carey Regarding Labor History, March 12, 1940; 11.
    - Carey Regarding Citizen's Council for National Defense, September 25, 1940; 12.
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, June 4, 1936; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Organization, July 27, 1936; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor and RCA Strikes, August 19, 1936; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues, September 24, 1936; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 19, 1936; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, October 29, 1936; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Indiana and Dayton Organization, February 4, 1937; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Evensville Organization, April 29, 1937; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Evansville and Local 1002, May 6, 1937; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding RCA and Mallory, June 2, 1937; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Evansville, July 19, 1937; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding Organization, July 23, 1937; 24.
    - Emspak Regarding Evansville and RCA, July 31, 1937; 25.
    - Emspak Regarding Indianapolis Power and Light, Dues and Fairbanks Morse Contracts, August 11, 1937; 26.
    - Emspak Regarding 1937 UE Convention, August 23, 1937; 27.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Local 1005, September 30, 1937; 28.
    - Emspak Regarding Indianapolis, RCA, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Evansville, October 30, 1937; 29.
    - Emspak Regarding Constitutions, December 18, 1939; 30.
    - Emspak Regarding Factionalism, Local 902 and Evansville, January 10, 1940; 31.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 917 and Factionalism, May 10, 1940; 32.
    - W. Jordan Regarding Evansville, April 14, 1937; 33.
  - District 9 Incoming William Yager Correspondence, June 20, 1937-January 3, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - James Matles Regarding Indianapolis RCA, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Servel Organization, October 6, 1937; 1.
    - Matles Regarding International Harvester, January 15, 1940; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Meisner Coil and Factionalism, February 20, 1940; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 16, 1940; 4.
    - Matles Telegram to Staff Members, September 13, 1937; 5.
    - Matles Regarding Personal, January 3, 1941; 6.
    - Albert Stonkus Regarding Organization, June 30, 1937; 7.
    - Stonkus Regarding Local 1008 Negotiations, September 25, 1937; 8.
    - Stonkus Telegram Regarding Indiana Power and Light, October 8, 1937; 9.
    - Carey Regarding District 10, Steelworkers Organizing Committee, Indianapolis and RCA, January 20, 1937; 10.
    - Carey Regarding District 10, International Brotherhood of Electical Workers, RCA and Indianapolis, February 23, 1937; 11.
    - Carey Regarding District 10, Fairbanks-Morse, Dues and Fred Gallow, May 13, 1937; 12.
    - Carey Regarding District 10, Organization, Indianapolis and General Executive Board, May 25, 1937; 13.
  - District 9 Outgoing William Yager Correspondence, April 13, 1936-July 29, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - William Yager to James Carey Regarding Organization and American Federation of Labor, April 13, 1936; 1.
    - Yager to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 1001 and Organization, May 29, 1936; 2.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Fairbanks-Morse, June 2, 1936; 3.
    - Yager to James Carey Regarding RCA Strikes and Mallory Negotiations, July 9, 1936; 4.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Mallory and Factionalism, July 23, 1936; 5.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor and Mallory, August 17, 1936; 6.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Local 1001 and Organization, September 16, 1936; 7.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, November 9, 1936; 8.
    - Yager to Carey Regarding Organization, November 26, 1936; 9.
    - Yager to James Matles Regarding Organization and Negotiations, July 16, 1937; 10.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Evansville, Staff Members, RCA and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 26, 1937; 11.
    - Yager to Albert Stonkus Regarding Local 1008 and National Labor Relations Board, September 24, 1937; 12.
    - Yager to Carey Regarding District 9 and Staff Members, January 16, 1937; 13.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Local 1001 and District Council, January 30, 1937; 14.
    - Yager to Carey Regarding Local 1001 Negotiations, Indianapolis RCA and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 17, 1937; 15.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Finances and Organization, April 15, 1937; 16.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Evansville, United Auto Workers, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, RCA and Fairbanks-Morse, April 18, 1937; 17.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Evansville, and Indianapolis and Mallory RCA, May 2, 1937; 18.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Fairbanks-Morse, May 5, 1937; 19.
    - Yager to Carey Regarding Locals 1001, 1002, 1003 and RCA, May 19, 1937; 20.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding General Electric Board, RCA, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and Evansville, Mallory and Sunbeam Organizations, May 23, 1937; 21.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Municipal Workers, Local 1001, Dues, Jewel Organization and Fairbanks-Morse Contracts with Credentials, July 29, 1937; 22.
  - District 9 Outgoing William Yager Correspondence, August 3, 1937-December 20, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - William Yager to James Carey Regarding Indianapolis Organization and 1937 UE Convention, August 3, 1937; 1.
    - Yager to Julius Emspak Regarding Indianapolis Power and Light, August 4, 1937; 2.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding 1937 UE Convention and Indianapolis and Evansville Organizations, August 26, 1937; 3.
    - Yager Telegram to Emspak Regarding Evansville, September 12, 1937; 4.
    - Yager Telegram to Albert Stonkus Regarding Negotiations, September 12, 1937; 5.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding District 9 and RCA Inter-union Rivalry, October 1, 1937; 6.
    - Yager Telegram Regarding Stonkus Regarding Local 1008, October 8, 1937; 7.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding Evansville and Indianapolis, October 19, 1937; 8.
    - Yager to James Matles Regarding District Council and Evansville, October 20, 1937; 9.
    - Yager to James Carey Regarding RCA, October 20, 1937; 10.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding District 9 and Officers with Officers Lists, October 27, 1937; 11.
    - Yager to Emspak Regarding District 9, January 4, 1940; 12.
    - Yager to Thurber Jones Regarding Evansville, January 19, 1940; 13.
    - Yager to Matles Regarding District 9, District Convention and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 17, 1940; 14.
    - Yager to Local 1001 with Questionnaire, 15.
    - Yager to Matles Regarding Officers, December 20, 1940; 16.
  - District 9 Incoming Edward Bunting Correspondence, April 6, 1936-September 1, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Morris Anweiler Telegram Regarding Magnavox Negotiations, December 11, 1937; 1.
    - James Carey Regarding Federal Local 19750, Organization and Dudur Amsco Strikes, April 6, 1936; 2.
    - Carey Telegram Regarding Strikes and Organization, July 1, 1936; 3.
    - Carey Regarding New Kensington General Electric, October 13, 1936; 4.
    - Carey Regarding Cabinet Industry, October 14, 1936; 5.
    - Carey Regarding Tampa Convention, November 25, 1936; 6.
    - Carey Regarding General Electric, February 18, 1937; 7.
    - Carey Regarding General Electric and General Executive Board, February 27, 1937; 8.
    - Carey Regarding General Electric Negotiations, March 3, 1937; 9.
    - Carey Regarding Michigan and Allis Chalmers, April 6, 1937; 10.
    - Carey Regarding General Electric Negotiations and Factionalism, September 25, 1937; 11.
    - Carey Regarding Local 901, Factionalism and District Council, November 1, 1937; 12.
    - Carey Regarding Finances, September 1, 1939; 13.
    - Lawrence Cover Regarding Local 915, American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, Wabash and Local 914, July 3, 1937; 14.
    - Cover Regarding Wabash and Local 914, July 11, 1937; 15.
    - Cover Regarding Wabash and United Rubber Workers, August 1, 1937; 16.
    - Cover Regarding Locals 905 and 707, and Wabash, October 4, 1937; 17.
    - Cover Regarding Bailey and McLaughlin Organization, October 9, 1937; 18.
    - Archie Dennings Regarding Local 724 and Grievances, September 1, 1938; 19.
    - John Dennis Regarding Local 901 and Factionalism, October 11, 1937; 20.
  - District 9 Incoming Edward Bunting Correspondence, April 22, 1946-July 17, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Locals 901 and 902, April 22, 1936; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 301 General Electric Strikes, June 3, 1936; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Fort Wayne Pump and Bridgeport General Electric, June 11, 1936; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 301 General Electric Strikes, June 15, 1936; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Dayton, June 17, 1936; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Camden RCA Strikes, Local 301 General Electric Negotiations, and Schenectady General Electric, June 27, 1936; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding UE Constitution and Camden RCA Strikes, June 29, 1936; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Wayne Pump and Camden RCA Strikes, July 3, 1936; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Mechanics Educational Society of America, Camden RCA Strikes, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Company Union, July 20, 1936; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Wayne Pump, Mechanics Educational Society of America and American Federation of Labor, July 30, 1936; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Mechanics Educational Society of America, August 4, 1936; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 903, August 14, 1936; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Horton, UE Convention and New Kensington General Electric Strikes, September 12, 1936; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Fort Wayne, Supplies and New Kensington General Electric Strikes, September 28, 1936; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding New Kensington General Electric Strikes, and Schenectady, Erie and Pittsfield General Electrics, December 19, 1936; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Auto Strikes and General Electric, February 11, 1937; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 912 and 913, June 23-30, 1937; 17-18.
    - Emspak Regarding Cabinet Industry, Staff Members and General Electric Contracts, July 1, 1937; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding International Association of Machinists South Bend Singer, July 17, 1937; 20.
  - District 9 Incoming Edward Bunting Correspondence, August 4, 1937-September 19, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, Ohio and General Electric Negotiations, August 4, 1937; 1.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Capehart, August 12, 1937; 2.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Lima Westinghouse and Company Union, August 18, 1937; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Philadelphia and Fort Wayne General Electrics, August 23, 1937; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding 1937 UE Convention, August 25, 1937; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding General Electric Negotiations with Proposed Contract, October 5, 1937; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Magnavox, November 15, 1937; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 911 Disbanding, April 12, 1938; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Local 901, Singer, Strikes and Maytag, July 21, 1938; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Taxis Organization, December 14, 1938; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Peoples Press and UE News, December 21, 1938; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Retail Clerks, Local 901 and Finances, January 6, 1939; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Decator General Electric, February 9, 1939; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, June 7, 1939; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding 1939 UE Convention, September 19, 1939; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding United Auto Workers Strikes, 16.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Schenectady Conference and Local 201, 17.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Capehart Strikes, 18.
    - R. A. Hoff Regarding Defiance and Lima, and National Labor Relations Board, August 6, 1937; 19.
    - John Lantow Regarding Local 727 Company Union, August 1, 1937; 20.
    - Lantow Regarding Local 727 and National Labor Relations Board, August 3, 1937; 21.
    - James Matles Regarding Singer Negotiations, October 7, 1937; 22.
  - District 9 Incoming Edward Bunting Correspondence, October 7, 1937-April 28, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - James Matles Telegram Regarding Carey Visit, October 7, 1937; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Furniture Industry, November 1, 1937; 2.
    - Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, November 2, 1937; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Singer Negotiations, November 26, 1937; 4.
    - Matles Regarding District 9, December 16, 1937; 5.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding General Electric, December 21, 1937; 6.
    - Matles Regarding Magnavox Negotiations, December 27, 1937; 7.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding National Labor Relations Board and General Electric, December 29, 1937; 8.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Magnavox Negotiations, January 31, 1938; 9.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Fort Wayne Visit, February 19, 1938; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 7, 1938; 11-12.
    - Matles Regarding General Electric, National Labor Relations Board and Singer Negotiations, March 15, 1938; 13.
    - Matles Regarding Distric Council, Factionalism and Per Capita, April 12, 1938; 14.
    - Matles Regarding Factionalism, Per Capita, Westinghosue and Inca and National Labor Relations Board Negotiations, April 21, 1938; 15.
    - Matles Regarding Company Union, Philadelphia and Inter-union Rivalry, April 29, 1938; 16.
    - Matles Regarding Fort Waynt General Electric, Pattern Markers and International Association of Machinists, May 6, 1938; 17.
    - Matles Regarding Local 1140 Electric Machinery Contract and Wages, July 2, 1938; 18.
    - Matles Regarding Singer and National Labor Relations Board, July 5, 1938; 19.
    - Matles Regarding Lima Westinghouse and Firings, September 26, 1938; 20.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Memers and Indianapolis, December 19, 1938; 21.
    - Matles Regarding Indianapolis, December 29, 1938; 22.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 7, 1939; 23.
    - Matles Regarding Michigan, April 24, 1939; 24.
    - Matles Regarding Servel Boycott, Essex Wine and Factionalism, April 28, 1939; 25.
  - District 9 Incoming Edward Bunting Correspondence, March 8-December 9, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - William Mitchell Telegram Regarding Carey Visit, October 15, 1937; 1.
    - Albert Stonkus Regarding Local 906 and National Labor Relations Board, December 9, 1937; 2.
    - Unsigned Letter Regarding Philadelphia General Electric, March 8, 1937; 3.
    - Unsigned Letter Regarding Local 908, April 23, 1937; 4.
    - Unsigned Letter Regarding Local 909, April 24, 1937; 5.
  - District 9 Outgoing Edward Bunting Correspondence, June 4, 1936-June 30, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Edward Bunting to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 603, May 17, 1937; 1.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding New York Trip, June 4, 1936; 2.
    - Bunting Telegram James Carey Regarding Wayne Pump, June 11-16, 1936; 3-4.
    - Bunting to Carey UE Constitution, June 25, 1936; 5.
    - Bunting Telegram to Carey Regarding Tokheim Pump Strikes, July 1, 1936; 6.
    - Bunting Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Horton Manufacturing, September 11, 1936; 7.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Pump Companies, September 13, 1936; 8.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding Horton and Magnavox, September 14, 1936; 9.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding 1936 UE Convention, September 16, 1936; 10.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Horton and Magnavox, Inter-union Rivalry and International Association of Machinists, September 23, 1936; 11.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Horton and Magnavox and New Kensington General Electric Negotiations, December 16, 1936; 12.
    - Bunting Telegram to Carey Regarding Bluffton, April 7, 1937; 13.
    - Bunting to Sarah Regarding Locals 906 and 907, April 19, 1937; 14.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Local 908, April 21, 1937; 15.
    - Bunting to Stella Abrams Regarding Local 909, April 22, 1937; 16.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding General Electric Negotiations, April 25, 1937; 17.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding Magnavox, Defiance and Carpenters Inter-union Rivalry, June 3, 1937; 18.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding Monticello and Carpenters Inter-union Rivalry, June 16, 1937; 19.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Monticello and Carpenters and Mechanics Educational Society of America inter-union Rivalry, June 24, 1937; 20.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Local 915 and Carpenters Inter-union Rivalry, June 25, 1937; 21.
    - Bunting Telegram to Carey Regarding Mass Meeting, June 30, 1937; 22.
  - District 9 Outgoing Edward Bunting Correspondence, July 9-October 22, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Edward Bunting to Julius Emspak Regarding Peru, Monticello, Wabash, Riders, Carpenters Inter-union Rivalry and General Electric Negotiations, July 9, 1937; 1.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, July 13, 1937; 2.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Fort Wayne General Electric, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, Wayne Pump and White Sewing Machine, July 14, 1937; 3.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Singer Machine and General Electric Negotiations, July 14, 1937; 4.
    - Bunting to James Carey Regarding Defiance, Lima and National Labor Relations Board, August 2, 1937; 5.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 909 Capehart Strikes, August 13, 1937; 6.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Defiance, National Labor Relations Board and Local 909 Capehart Negotiations, August 6, 1937; 7.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding Capehart Strikes, August 13, 1937; 8.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Local 909 Capehart Strikes, August 17, 1937; 9.
    - Bunting to Carey Regarding United Rubber Workers, Factionalism, Local 901, Locals 907 and 909 Capehart Strikes, and General Electric Negotiations, September 18, 1937; 10.
    - Bunting to Carey Regarding Local 901 and Factionalism, September 30, 1937; 11.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding Carey Visit, October 1, 1937; 12.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 2, 1937; 13.
    - Bunting Telegram to James Matles Regarding Carey Visit, October 7, 1937; 14.
    - Bunting to Matles Regarding District Council and Staff Members, October 12, 1937; 15.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding International Radio, October 13, 1937; 16.
    - Bunting Telegram to Carey Regarding Carey Visit, October 14, 1937; 17.
    - Bunting to Matles Regarding Fort Wayne General Electric, National Labor Relations Board, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry and Federal Local 18529, October 22, 1937; 18.
  - District 9 Outgoing Edward Bunting Correspondence, November 9, 1937-June 15, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Edward Bunting to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Factionalism, Local 901 and Magnavox and Fairbanks-Morse, November 9, 1937; 1.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Local 916, November 12, 1937; 2.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, November 15, 1937; 3.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Cleveland General Electric, Factionalism, and Locals 901 and 913, November 26, 1937; 4.
    - Bunting to James Carey Regarding Magnavox Negotiations and Wages, December 2, 1937; 5.
    - Bunting to Carey Regarding Magnavox Negotiations and Bankrupcy, December 14, 1937; 6.
    - Bunting to James Matles Regarding Singer and National Labor Relations Board, December 24, 1937; 7.
    - Bunting to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, General Electric and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, December 29, 1937; 8.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Fort Wayng General Electric and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, January 21, 1938; 9.
    - Bunting to UE Regarding Local 916, January 26, 1938; 10.
    - Bunting to UE Regarding District Council, February 1938; 11.
    - Bunting to Matles Regarding Singer, Singer Negotiations, National Labor Relations Board, and Unemployment, March 11, 1938; 12.
    - Bunting Telegram to Matles Regarding General Electric, International Association of Machinists and National Labor Relations Board, March 15, 1938; 13.
    - Bunting to Matles Regarding Local 901 and Unemployment, March 23, 1938; 14.
    - Bunting to National Office Regarding Staff Members, April 13, 1938; 15.
    - Bunting to Matles Regarding Per Capita, DIstrict 9, General Electric, Singer and Capehart, April 18, 1938; 16.
    - Bunting Telegram to Carey Regarding Retail Employees, April 22, 1938; 17.
    - Bunting Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 707, April 25, 1938; 18.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Unemployment, May 4, 1938; 19.
    - Bunting Telegram to Matles Regarding Singer, May 18, 1938; 20.
    - Bunting to Jim Regarding Staff Members, Unemployment and General Electric Negotiations, May 31, 1938; 21.
    - Bunting to Matles Regarding Westinghouse and Lima, June 15, 1938; 22.
  - District 9 Outgoing Edward Bunting Correspondence, July 11, 1938-April 21, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Edward Bunting to UE Regarding Unemployment, Fort Wayne General Electric and Per Capita, July 11, 1938; 1.
    - Bunting to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 903, August 6, 1938; 2.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Capehart with Constitution and By-Laws on Back, August 29, 1938; 3.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Fort Wayne General Electric and Unemployment, October 27, 1938; 4.
    - Bunting to Jim Regarding Staff Members and Indianapolis, December 14, 1938; 5.
    - Bunting to UE Regarding Peoples Press and Factionalism, December 16, 1938; 6.
    - Bunting to UE Regarding Finances and Retail Clerks, January 4, 1939; 7.
    - Bunting to Al Regarding Staff Members, Evansville, Essex Wire, General Electric and Employment, February 8, 1939; 8.
    - Bunting to Al Regarding Publicity and United Auto Workers, February 11, 1939; 9.
    - Bunting Telegram to James Matles Regarding Evansville, March 17, 1939; 10.
    - Bunting to Jim Regarding Local 1002, Boycott, Servel and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, April 21, 1939; 11.
  - District 9 Outgoing Edward Bunting Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Edward Bunting to Jimmie Regarding General Electric and RCA, 1.
    - Bunting to Julius Emspak Regarding General Electric Conference, 1936; 2.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Mausfield Westinghouse Strikes and Carey Visit, 3.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Organization, Local 901, Dues and Local 903 Officers, 4.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Peru Square D and Women, 5.
    - Bunting to Jimmie Regarding Factionalism and Local 901, 6.
    - Bunting to Emspak Regarding Dayton and Local 901, 7.